statsalt.com 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy - Winners & Whiners

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for statsalt.com, hereafter referred to as the "Site". This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

###  Security Practices 

All information is transmitted using SSL certificates with industry standard encryption methods. Information that we collect directly is stored using industry standard practices. 

###  Registration & Logging In 

Limited content requires users to register an account and be logged in to view. The vast majority of content is free and available without an account. When registering, users are required to provide an email. This email is used to provide updates from our site and select sponsors. If you wish to opt out of this, do not register an account. 

###  Cookies 

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. If you login, we use a Cookie to identify you in order to provide access to user only content. Regardless of whether or not you are logged in, cookies on our site never contain personally identifiable information. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. If you believe any of our partners maybe misusing your information, please contact us so we may investigate. 

###  Links 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

However, contact us so we may investigate any links on our site that maybe leading to sites that are misusing personally identifiable information. 

###  Requesting changes to your information 

If you wish to change information related to your account, or to have your account removed and associated information deleted from our system, please contact us via mail or phone using the information provided on our contact page with details regarding your request. 

### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. 

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone which can be found on our contact page.
